(Leonard:)Oh, so she's an astronomer?
(Raj:)Yes...
(Raj:)which is why she was
in the telescope room.
(Raj:)Yes, this is all making sense.
(Raj:)Good.
(Penny:)Well, that's great, Raj.
(Penny:)You must have
so much in common.
(Raj:)Mm-hmm.
(Howard:)So, when do we meet her?
No, no, this is brand-new.
(Raj:)We haven't even been
on a proper date yet.
(Leonard:)Okay, well, good luck with it.
Thank you.
(Penny:)How come you
never eat broccoli?
(Leonard:)I'm married,
(Leonard:)I don't have to be attractive.
(Amy:)You know, most
people don't realize
(Amy:)this technique has
actually been around
(Amy:)for a few years.
(Bernadette:)Still, I can't believe
you can turn ordinary skin cells
(Bernadette:)into functioning brain cells.
(Amy:)Well, I turned this one
into a functioning boyfriend,
(Amy:)so sky's the limit.
(Sheldon:)Look, look... here I am
(Sheldon:)standing next
to the incubator.
(Sheldon:)Uh, here is a microscopic
view of the cells.
(Bernadette:)Look at that, put them in a tiny
Flash T-shirt and it's you.